{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839870426","data":{"timestamp":" 946839870426"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839879985","data":{"timestamp":" 946839879985"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839880208","data":{"timestamp":" 946839880208"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839881171","data":{"timestamp":" 946839881171"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839882442","data":{"timestamp":" 946839882442"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839885283","data":{"timestamp":" 946839885282"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839886125","data":{"timestamp":" 946839886125"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839886438","data":{"timestamp":" 946839886438"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839887671","data":{"timestamp":" 946839887671"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839891147","data":{"timestamp":" 946839891147"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839892128","data":{"timestamp":" 946839892128"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839892380","data":{"timestamp":" 946839892380"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839893323","data":{"timestamp":" 946839893323"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839896151","data":{"timestamp":" 946839896151"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839897183","data":{"timestamp":" 946839897183"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839897656","data":{"timestamp":" 946839897656"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839902164","data":{"timestamp":" 946839902164"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839902223","data":{"timestamp":" 946839902223"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839909742","data":{"timestamp":" 946839909742"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 3058174f-a8c3-45ca-9c72-4ca5166371b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839925032","data":{"timestamp":" 946839925031"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839930744","data":{"timestamp":" 946839930744"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839936798","data":{"timestamp":" 946839936798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839941720","data":{"timestamp":" 946839941720"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839965900","data":{"timestamp":" 946839965900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946839973742","data":{"timestamp":" 946839973742"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946840003024","data":{"timestamp":" 946840003024"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946840008573","data":{"timestamp":" 946840008573"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946840015046","data":{"timestamp":" 946840015046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946840023513","data":{"timestamp":" 946840023513"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946840064846","data":{"timestamp":" 946840064846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_220414"," gameId":" 4092dc8f-71b0-4355-818b-7635458c08e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}